

md.balaka@gmail.com

Haifa, Israel

+972 58-406-2924

https://dmytro-balakin.onrender.com/

Profile

Hello, my name is Dmytro Balakin and I am looking for a position of a junior Python developer. I am 29 years old, originally from Ukraine, currently located in Israel. After making a career in medicine from an assistant surgeon in Kharkiv Emergency hospital (Ukraine), through intern doctor in Rambam Medical Centre (Haifa, Israel), to a head of one of the IDF clinics, I am now taking a new turn in my life eager to work in high tech sphere. I am a hardworking, proactive and dedicated employee that was proved by all the employers I worked for since the age of 18.

Employment History

Laboratory assistant at the faculty of computer science, Kharkiv National Karazin University

2016 - 2018

- · Analysis of patient databases.
- · Understanding relationships between databases.
- Development of simple applications for working with databases of patient diseases.

Head of the audit committee, GAMMA 55 company, Kharkiv, Ukraine

2017 - 2019

- Working with a pharmacy chain's drug database.
- · Analysis and processing of prices for medicines.
- Auditing of medications and other health-related products in a chain of pharmacies.
- · Prepare comprehensive audit reports that detailed the results of the audit and identified potential risks.

Assistant surgeon, Kharkiv Emergency Hospital, Kharkiv, Ukraine

2018 — 2019

- Participating in a variety of surgeries as an assistant.
- Performing minor primary and secondary surgeries.
- Follow up of the patients.

Head of the clinic, IDF, Israel

2022 - 2023

- · Primary treatment of soldiers.
- Managing and optimizing performance of the clinic.
- · Teaching and providing training of MTLS protocols.
- Scheduled patient appointments and managed the flow of the clinic to ensure efficient patient care.

Languages

Ukranian	Russian
Hebrew	English

Education

Doctor of medcine

2012 — 2018

Kharkiv National Karazin University

Kharkiv, Ukraine

Python Institute (Open Education and Development Group)

January 2023 — March 2023

Wilmington, DE, 19805, United States

Python Essentials course - General-Purpose Programming (Certified Entry-Level Python Programmer (Exam PCEP-30-0x) and Certified Associate in Python Programming (Exam PCAP-31-0x)

Master of Computer Science: Software Engineering

2023 — Present

WOOLF global collegiate higher education institution.

San Francisco, California

Courses

The Complete Guide to Python 3: From Beginner to Expert, Udemy (39 total hours)

September 2023

Python development - from scratch to professional. Python 3, Udemy (40 total hours)

November 2022

Python 3 - GUI development with PyQt5, Udemy (18.5 total hours)

December 2022

Data Science and Machine Learning Python, Udemy (19.5 total hours)

January 2023

Machine Learning and Data Science, Udemy (50.5 total hours)

July 2023

100 Days of Code: The Complete Python Pro Bootcamp for 2023, Udemy (58 total hours)

October 2023

Skills

Python	Git, GitHub
PyQt5, Tkinter	Seaborn, Matplotlib, Plotly
SQL	Flask
SciKit Learn	HTML
Selenium	Pandas, NumPy

Links

More information on my Personal Website